jroo.me 2011-12-03

# Privacy Policy - Jokeroo

**Jokeroo.com Privacy Policy**  
This Site is operated by JMG - Jolt Media Group.   
You may contact us at: support (at) jokeroo.com 

**Jokeroo.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Jokeroo.com.

 **Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information to help us better serve you.

 **Advertisers**

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).

 **Information Collected**

We collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page and site registrations. The information we collect is used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site. Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the below address. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the below address.

 **Cookies**

We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information. If you are interested in **opting-out** , please visit [networkadvertising.org](http://http//www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

 **Third Party Cookies**

Notwithstanding any other provision in this policy, in visiting this site or opening an email you have received from us, a third-party advertiser (or its partners) may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. These cookies enable more customized ads, content or services to be provided to you. To trigger these cookies, we may pass an encrypted or "hashed" (non-human readable) identifier corresponding to your email address to a Web advertising partner, who may place a cookie on your computer. No personally identifiable information is on, or is connected to, these cookies. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to <http://www.privacychoice.org/companies> or <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

 **Security**

We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site.

 **External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. Jokeroo.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 **Enforcement**

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the following email address: support (at) jokeroo.com

 **Notification of Changes**

If we change this privacy policy, we will post those changes on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
